It’s easy to customise your notes.

Make your notes stand out and get noticed.

• Format text using different fonts and font sizes
• Add emphasis with bold and italic text styles or colour.
• Include graphics ￼ . 

Stickies has lots of other great features, including a spellchecker, import and export features, and other ways to arrange and customise your notes. Plus, you’ll find a “Make New Sticky Note” service in many applications.

Look in Help to find out more about using Stickies.